satyamevjayate.in 2018-05-11

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers the information Star India Private Limited ("STAR" and/or "We") collects from the user(s) ("User(s)" and/or "You") of [www.satyamevjayate.in](http://www.satyamevjayate.in/) (" **Website** ") and how We handle and/or deal in the Personal Information provided by You in the course of the use of the Website by You . This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with the Terms of Service available on <http://www.satyamevjayate.in/termsofuse.aspx> This Privacy Policy is applicable throughout the world and is deemed to be effective as of January 26th.

By registering on the Website, You agree to allow us use of your Personal Information, as defined below, in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy determines, _inter alia_ , how We deal in and/or handle the Personal Information provided by You, the purposes for which We may use such Personal Information, correction of inaccuracies in the Personal Information by You, withdrawal of consent to use Personal Information by You.

The Website is owned by Aamir Khan Productions Private Limited (" **Production House** "), and is licensed to STAR for the purpose of the management, operation and development of the Website and the provision of services to You.

Here are our privacy principles, which have been dealt with in greater detail below:

  * Providing information to us is your choice.
  * You can choose to review, correct and delete the Personal Information (defined later) You have provided to us.
  * You always have the ability to opt-out of receiving communications from us.

The Personal Information provided by You is used by STAR to increase the quality of the Website and the services provided by STAR to You. In the event that You do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and/or the collection of the Personal Information by STAR as stipulated in this Privacy Policy, please do not access and/or use the Website and/or avail the services provided by STAR. If you refuse to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, We may choose not to offer You the services for which the Personal Information was being collected.

### Information Collection and Use

The information which You may provide to us or which We may collect is or could be the following:

  * Your registration details which may include details such as your name, age, gender, location/pin code, email address, mobile number and the password provided by You ("Personal Information"). You may note that We adopt reasonable security measures to protect Your Personal Information from being exposed or disclosed to anyone including being disclosed on the Website;
  * Information that you post/upload on the Website which may include but is not limited to messages, board posts, reviews, blogs, ratings, data, notes and testimonials, poll votes, images, audio or video files and any software (" **User Content** ");
  * Your usage of the Website;
  * Details of the computer system or computer network which You use to visit the Website and undertake any activity on the Website; and
  * Any other information which whether individually or in combination with any other information is capable of identifying You.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, the term " **Personal Information** " shall not include any information which is not capable of identifying You either individually and/or in combination with any other information.

Our primary purpose in collecting information from You is to allow You to use the Website along with the various services and products available on the Website. We may also use the information for transactional emails or to provide You with information, direct marketing, online and offline advertising and other materials regarding products, services and other offers from time to time in connection with STAR or its parent, subsidiary and affiliate companies (" **STAR Entities** ") and its joint ventures. We may also collect information to track User behavior and preferences for internal analytics from all Users of the Website. This information is collected through the use of server log files and tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information and may include cookies and web beacons.  
We may combine your Personal Information and information collected from tracking technologies and aggregate it with information collected from other Users using our Website to attempt to provide You with a better experience on our Website. You understand, agree and acknowledge that our collection, storage and processing of your Personal Information is for a lawful purpose connected with a function or activity of the STAR Entities and its joint ventures.

If You do not consent to the use of cookies by STAR, You may at any time adjust Your browser settings and/or delete and/or disable the cookies. However, please note that should You choose to delete/ disable the use of cookies on Your computer, certain sections of the Website and/or services provided by STAR may not be available to You.

### Consent to Personal Information -

You hereby consent to the collection, storage, use, disclosure, transfer, of the Personal Information by STAR for the purposes of this Privacy Policy. You hereby agree and acknowledge that the collection, storage, use, disclosure, transfer, of the Personal Information by STAR under the terms of this Privacy Policy is for a lawful purpose and is necessary for the provision of services to You on the Website.

You further understand, agree and acknowledge that your Personal Information may be classified as sensitive personal information such as Your password, age, physiological details, sexual orientation, bank account and credit card details, under applicable laws as is considered necessary by STAR to provide access to various services on its Website to You and for your usage of the Website.

### Withdrawal of Consent:

You may at any time withdraw Your consent to the collection, storage, use, disclosure, transfer, of the Personal Information and/or the sensitive personal data or information by STAR, by addressing a written communication to this effect to the contact address of the Grievance Officer specified below. However, You agree and acknowledge that in the event that You choose to so withdraw Your consent, STAR shall be entitled to not provide any or all of the services on the Website to You.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure:

STAR is the recipient of all the Personal Information including any sensitive personal data or information and shall exercise reasonable commercial endeavors for the prevention of unauthorized disclosure of the Personal Information including any sensitive personal data or information provided by the Users. We may enable access of the Users' information to the STAR Entities or its joint ventures, agents or third parties in relation to the Website or for any other marketing related activity undertaken by or on behalf of the STAR Entities and/or its joint ventures and/or for the purposes of enhancing the quality of the services provided to You on the Website. We will ensure on reasonable commercial efforts basis that the third parties and agents employed by us maintain confidentiality with respect to the Personal Information including any sensitive personal data or information provided by the Users and use it strictly for the purposes specified herein.

The name and address of the agency that is collecting and retaining the information is:

Star India Pvt. Ltd.Star House, Urmi Estate, 95 Ganpatrao Kadam Marg, Lower Parel (W), Mumbai, 400013.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement:

STAR cooperates with mandated government and law enforcement agencies or with any third parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about You to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as We, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal processes, to protect the property and rights of the STAR Entities or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. STAR may also provide your Personal Information including any sensitive personal data or information to various tax authorities upon any demand or request from them. You understand and agree that STAR may provide and/or disclose your Personal Information or sensitive personal information to such third parties as it deems fit, such as press, news media, local authorities for the bonafide purpose of, inter alia, investigation into any User Content uploaded on the Website.

### Business Transfers:

STAR may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information including any sensitive personal data or information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will ensure that the Personal Information including any sensitive personal data or information You have provided through the Website is stored and used by the transferee in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### Email Policies:

STAR may use the e-mail ID provided by You for the purposes mentioned in this Privacy Policy. You have full control regarding which of these emails You want to receive. If You decide at any time that You no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. Please note that once we receive your request, it may take an additional reasonable period of time for Your opt-out to become effective.

### Security:

STAR uses ordinary industry standard technology designed to help keep your Personal Information including sensitive personal data or information safe. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information You put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data We collect is protected against unauthorized access. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, We will employ commercially reasonable and practicable security practices and procedures and security methods and technologies. We will also ensure on reasonable commercial efforts basis that any agent or third party that We employ complies with the same security standards as us for the protection of your Personal Information including any sensitive personal information or data.  
Your information may be transferred to or be maintained on computers, computer systems and computer resources located outside of your state or country where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those where you live. If You are located outside India and choose to provide information to us, please be aware that STAR keeps or transfers information to India and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although We strive to protect your personal data, We cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once We have received your information, We have commercially reasonable procedures and security features in place to reasonably endeavor to prevent unauthorized access.

### Changes in Personal Information and/or sensitive personal data or information:

You shall be entitled at any time to review and correct any deficiencies/ discrepancies/ defects/ errors in the Personal Information and/or sensitive personal data or information provided by You by addressing a written request to this effect to the contact address of the Grievance Officer specified below.

However, You understand and acknowledge that STAR shall not at any time be responsible and/or liable in any manner for the authenticity and/or accuracy of the Personal Information including the sensitive personal data or information provided by You.

### Changes in Privacy Policy:

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website constitutes an acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions so We encourage You to visit this page periodically to review any changes.

### Phishing:

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to STAR. Safeguarding information to help protect You from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

### Public Postings:

Any and all Personal Information including sensitive personal data or information available in the User Content uploaded by You on the Website shall be Your sole responsibility, given the publicly available nature of such User Content. While We shall endeavor to ensure that the terms of this Privacy Policy shall be available to all features/ sections of the Website, You shall be deemed to have waived the confidentiality to any Personal Information including sensitive personal information and data comprised in the User Content and any other publicly available information on the Website.

### Third party websites:

We may provide links/ information relating to third party websites to You for Your use and convenience. In the event that You choose to access/ use such third party websites, You agree and acknowledge that the privacy policy and terms of use of such third party websites shall be applicable to the access and use of such third party websites by You. You hereby agree and acknowledge that We and/or the Production House shall not be responsible and/or liable for any Personal Information and/or sensitive personal data or information collected by such third party websites from You.

### Contact Us:

If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of STAR or your dealings with the Website, You can contact us via the links at the bottom of the page, or by writing to [hello@startv.com](mailto:hello@startv.com).

### Grievance Officer:

Mr. Manu Anand shall be the Grievance Officer for the purpose of this Privacy Policy. If You have any question or grievance or want to delete or modify your Personal Information, You shall mark your correspondence to the email ID provided in the name of Manu Anand Grievance Officer- [manu.anand@startv.com](mailto:manu.anand@startv.com). Any communication which is not marked as such shall not be treated as a valid and binding communication for the purpose of this Privacy Policy and applicable laws.

This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.
